diversityinc.com 2012-05-29

# Privacy Policy - Corporate Diversity, Diversity in the Workplace, Diversity Benchmarking, Diversity Metrics, Diversity Consulting, Diversity Management, Diversity and Inclusion, Diversity Magazine, Diversity Events, Diversity Web Seminars, Diversity Articles, Diversity in Business

We are strongly committed to safeguarding subscribers’ privacy on DiversityIncBestPractices.com. We operate under the following strict privacy policy:

The only information we obtain about our subscribers is information we need to process credit-card charges for subscription fees. The information collected is never revealed, sold or made public for any reason.

Personally identifiable information provided by subscribers (name, email or home address, etc.) is never disclosed to any individual or business.

**Cookies**  
Each time a subscriber logs into DiversityIncBestPractices.com, we store a temporary “cookie” in the browser files of that subscriber’s computer. This cookie is used during your online session to allow you free access to the subscribers area, without repeatedly requiring you to re-enter your user name and password.

When you log off or leave the site, the cookie file is automatically removed.

**External Links**  
In order to provide visitors with greater value, some of our pages may provide links to various third-party websites. Subscriber information and “cookies” are not provided to the third-party sites.

However, keep in mind that many sites do attempt to capture visitor information when you browse those sites. Once you leave our site, we are not able to alert you should another site attempt to gather information from your browser.

**Private Forums**  
We provide our subscribers with a comment feature that makes sharing information with other subscribers easy. To protect your privacy when posting or replying to comments, your personal information and email are not revealed.

However, remember that any information you disclose in the message areas can be read by all other subscribers, so exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Security**  
We use a variety of security measures including encryption and authentication from Thawte to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of your personal information under our control.

**Choice/Opt-In**  
Our site gives users the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. You can be assured that we never reveal, sell or make available your email address to anyone for any purpose. This site also gives users options for removing their information from our database in order to stop receiving our communications.

**Federal & State Law**  
DiversityInc will share information with the government when required by law. DiversityInc will not share information unless it has been given a valid court order or subpoena. DiversityInc will not disclose whether or not law-enforcement agencies have sought or obtained information under the Patriot Act.

**Other**  
If you have questions regarding our privacy policy, feel free to contact us.
